(ヤマト)カカシ先輩。
Kakashi-senpai...
(カカシ)かすかでも アイツの➡
If there is even a faint scent
that lingers from Sasuke...
サスケのにおいが
残っているというのなら…。
Yeah... that's right.
(ナルト)ああ そうだ。
No way can we give up
after coming this far.
ここまで来て
あきらめられるかっての！
最後まで あがこう。
サスケのにおいが完全に消えるまで。
We'll see this through until the end.
Until there's absolutely
no trace of Sasuke's scent.
Byakugan!
《ヒナタ : 白眼！》
(ヒナタ)いない… お願い！
Nothing... Please, find him.
Sasuke-kun...
《サクラ : サスケ君…》
ク～ン。
Yeah... I know.
(キバ)ああ… わかってる。
サスケのにおいが完全に消えた…。
There's no trace of Sasuke's scent.
Dammit...
クソッ！
Where did you go?
《どこ行っちまったんだ》
できるかぎりのことはやった。
戻ろう 木ノ葉へ。
We've done what we could...
Let's go back to the Hidden Leaf...
《サスケ…》
Sasuke...
i realise the screaming pain
hearing loud in my brain
but i'm going straight ahead with the scar
I should just get over it and I should just stop feeling it
wasurete shimaeba ii yo kanjinaku nacchaeba ii
and so I covered my grazed heart
surimuita kokoro ni futa wo shitan da
I don't care if I'm hurt 'cause I don't feel pain anymore
kizutsuitatte heki da yo mou itami wa nai kara ne
all while you limped on while dragging your feet behind you
sono ashi wo hikizuri nagara mo
I had lost sight of myself
miushinatta jibun jishin ga
which had crumbled loudly to the ground
oto wo taete kuzureteita
but then I realised it was just the sound of the wind...
kizukeba kaze no oto dake ga
I came here to tell you something following my deep scars
tsutae ni kita yo kizuato wo tadotte
before I am completely crushed by this vast world
sekai ni oshitsubusarete shimau mae ni
do you remember that sky of tears
oboeteru kana namida no sora wo
that pain protected you for me
ano itami ga kimi no koto wo mamotte kureta
that pain is always protecting you
sono itami ga itsumo kimi wo mamotterunda
can you hear me so am i
Battle of Unraikyo
(マダラ)何してる？ 準備は
とっくに整っているんだぞ。
What are you doing?
The preparations are already complete.
(サスケ)こうして満月を見ていると
あの夜のことを思い出す。
When I look upon the full moon,
it takes me back to that night.
それに
忘れようとしていた記憶もな。
As well as...
the memories I've been trying to forget.
今ならイタチのことを思い出せる。
Now I can finally recall things
about Itachi...
自分の心の奥にしまいこんでた
かすかな記憶が➡
Faint memories buried deep in my heart
よみがえってくるんだ。
are floating back to the surface.
((イタチ : 逃げて逃げて…
生に しがみつくがいい。
Run... keep running...
and cling to life.
そして いつかオレと同じ眼をもって
オレの前に来い！
Then one day,
come before me with
the same eye that I possess.
(待て！))
Wait!
あのとき泣いていた。
He was crying at that moment.
見間違いだと思った。
I thought I had imagined it.
オレは 気づけなかった。
I didn't realize...
どうやら アンタの言ったことは
本当だったようだ。
It seems what you told me was true.
(マダラ)どうする？
イタチの眼は移植するのか？
So what will you do?
Are you going to transplant Itachi's eyes?
いいや。
No...
イタチの見たかったものと
これから オレが見ていくものは➡
What Itachi wanted to see,
and what I will see hereafter,
まるで 違うものになる。
will be completely different.
イタチが望んだとおりにはできない。
I can't do as Itachi wished me to do.
オレは オレのやり方で
うちはを再興する。
I will restore the Uchiha clan
in my own way.
(トビ)あ… あの！
鬼鮫先輩にお話があるんですけど。
Umm... I need to talk to you,
Kisame Senpai.
(鬼鮫)ゼツが ジャマしにきて
次は お前ですか。
First Zetsu,
now you come bothering me?
死んだと思ってましたがね。
I actually thought you were dead.
(マダラ)結局
最後になってしまったが➡
It turns out that you will be
the last to know.
いちばん身近なお前を騙していて
すまなかった。
I'm sorry that I had to deceive you,
the person closest to me.
Hmm?
そういうことでしたか。
So that's how it was.
トビが まさか あなただとは
思いませんでしたよ。
I never would have guessed
that Tobi was you.
これで 安心しました。
But I'm relieved...
If you're the one pulling the strings,
that makes it easier for me...
あなたが黒幕なら
私も立ち回りやすい。
Former Mizukage-sama...
I mean, Madara.
元水影様… いや マダラさん。
これからも頼むぞ 鬼鮫。
I shall continue to count on you, Kisame.
こちらこそ。
The same goes for me.
《イタチが抜けて… フフフ！
Itachi is out...
今度は その弟が…。
おもしろい めぐり合わせだ》
And now, his little brother joins.
What an interesting turn of events.
オレたち 鷹は 木ノ葉を潰す。
We, Taka, will destroy the Hidden Leaf.
You say that, but how do you intend
to go about it?
と 言っても
具体的に どう狙っていく？
殺るのは 上層部だ。 それ以外は
基本的に対象としない。
We're going to kill the Elders.
The others are not
our immediate concern.
上を狙えば 下が盾になる。
そう簡単にはいきませんよ。
If you aim high,
the ones below will shield them.
It won't be that easy.
あなたたち 鷹とやらだけでは
戦力不足ですね。
You so-called "Taka" don't have
enough strength for that.
(水月)鬼鮫先輩… ボクたちを
あまり なめないほうがいい。
Kisame-senpai...
You shouldn't underestimate us.
あのときの遊びの決着は
まだ ついてないし…。
We still haven't settled that
last game of ours.
今度は 本気で…。
This time, I'm serious...
(重吾)やめろ 水月！
Stop it, Suigetsu!
サスケ！ しつけが なっていないぞ。
Sasuke! You haven't trained them well.
《コイツを 腕だけで…》
He stopped it with just his arm...!
(香燐)水月 テメエ バカじゃねえのか!?
こんなとこで！
Suigetsu! Are you stupid?
This isn't the place to...
My objective is his Shark Skin Sword!
ボクの目的は そこの鮫肌だ！
I've been hanging with Sasuke only
so I could get that!
ソイツを手に入れるために
サスケに くっついてただけだ!!
サスケ！ どうするんだ？
Sasuke... What'll you do?
わかった。
やりたきゃ 勝手にやれ 水月。
All right...
Go for it if you want to, Suigetsu.
どうせ
今は まだ ソイツには勝てない。
You probably can't beat him
yet anyway.
《フフ… まだ ね》
Yet, huh?
おぉ～！ 言うね サスケ。
Oh... thanks a lot, Sasuke.
まぁ 待っててよ。
Just hold tight.
そのうち おいしいフカヒレでも
食べさせてあげるからさ。
I'll treat you to some tasty shark's fin
soon enough.
暁も戦力不足だ。
今は ムダな小競り合いは避けたい。
The Akatsuki is also low on manpower.
I'd like to avoid unnecessary skirmishes.
フン！ 人のことばっか
言えないね アンタら。
Humph. Then you shouldn't
criticize others, you guys.
我々の利害は一致する。
We share common interests.
これより 鷹は
暁と行動を共にしてもらう。
From here on, Taka will work together
with the Akatsuki.
その話に オレたちが乗る見返りは？
And what's in it for us?
尾獣をやる。
We'll give you a Tailed Beast.
尾獣？
Tailed Beast?
何も知らないのか？
You don't know about them?
あれだろ？
九尾の仲間みたいなもんで➡
I know! It's like the Nine-Tails,
尾に チャクラの塊が
具現化したっていう バ…。
with chakra physically manifesting
as tails, they're mon-
つまり なんだ？
In other words?
チャクラの化け物だ。
もともとは 初代 火影が➡
They're chakra monsters.
Originally, the First Hokage collected
several of them
いくつか集めて
コントロール下に置いたものだ。
and kept them under his control.
忍界大戦のたびに 火影柱間は
それらの条約や協定の証しに➡
Each time a Great Ninja War threatened,
the Hokage Hashirama used them
to maintain the power balance
and distributed them to other lands,
starting with the five great nations,
五大国をはじめとする
他国に分配し➡
パワーバランスを取ってきた。
as proof of alliances or agreements.
究極のチャクラ兵器といってもいい。
You could call them
the ultimate chakra weapons.
悪くない条件だろう？
It's not a bad preposition.
気前がいいな。
That's quite generous.
ただし 暁を裏切れば
ちゃんと死んでもらう。
However, if you betray the Akatsuki,
you will die accordingly.
フン。
Humph...
この世に尾獣は ９匹いますが➡
There are nine Tailed Beasts
in this world.
今は ６匹まで
暁が集めてますから あと３匹。
The Akatsuki has collected six so far...
so there are three left.
オレたちと鷹で
残り３匹を手分けして狩る。
The Akatsuki and Taka will split up
to hunt the remaining three.
それが 我々の当面の目的だ。
That is our immediate goal.
九尾は まだなんだろう？
You don't have the Nine-Tails yet, right?
鷹は 八尾を狩れ。
残りは 暁が狩る。
Taka will capture the Eight-Tails.
The Akatsuki will hunt the rest.
Which includes Naruto...
ナルトもな。
(ゼツ)どうだ？
(マダラ)うまくいった。
How did it go?
It went well...
(ゼツ)それは よかったな。
That's good.
イタチも死んだ。
目の上のコブは もういない。
Itachi is dead...
So our eyesore's finally gone.
木ノ葉に手を出さない
という条件も これで白紙だ。
And now,
we need no longer keep our pact
to stay away from the Hidden Leaf.
ずいぶん 待ったね。
We've waited so long...
計画どおりに進めるためだ。
これで いい。
All so we could proceed
according to plan.
This is fine.
イタチは やはり
サスケに保険をかけていた。
But Itachi had placed insurance
in Sasuke.
天照だ。
The Amaterasu.
イタチのヤツ 自分の真相を
知られてるとは➡
Itachi believed that no one knew
the truth about him.
思ってなかったんだろ。
なんで そこまで…。
So why go so far...?
真相うんぬんは抜きにしても
オレが サスケを➡
True intentions aside,
仲間に引き入れることも
危惧していたんだろう。
he probably feared I would try
to recruit Sasuke.
しかし ここまで来るのに➡
But... who would have thought
これほど
暁のメンバーがやられるとはな。
that the Akatsuki would lose so
many members to get to this point.
どこかしらに問題はあったが
みな己の意志で貢献をしてくれた。
We had problems at every turn...
But everyone made a valuable contribution
in their own way.
デイダラ。
Deidara... Sasori... Hidan... Kakuzu...
サソリ。
飛段 角都…。
彼らなくして
ここまでの進展はなかった。
Without them,
we could not have gotten this far.
そのお陰で オレのシナリオどおりに
事は運んでいる。
Thanks to them, the scenario is
playing out just as I planned.
何より サスケを手なずけた。
Most importantly...
I've won Sasuke over.
うっ…。
で 八尾ってのは どこにいる？
So? Where is this thing called
"Eight-Tails"?
我ら一族を ナメるな…。
Don't take us lightly...
お前らのような輩に
何も教える気はない！
We have no intention
of telling you a thing.
くっ… 夜月一族は 決して
仲間を裏切ったりはしない…。
We, the Yotsuki clan,
never betray our comrades.
それが…。
怯える心には 隙が生じる。
That is-
Doubt exists... in a fearful heart.
あっ…。
水月 もういいぜ。 サスケの幻術だ。
Suigetsu, enough.
He's under Sasuke's genjutsu.
チェッ… ここからが
いたぶりがいがあったのにさ。
Shucks... I was just getting
to the fun part.
八尾の居場所を教えろ。
Tell me where the Eight-Tails is.
雲雷峡にて…
修業を… されている…。
He is training... at Unraikyo,
Storm Cloud Ravine.
ソイツの特徴は？
Any distinguishing features?
８本の剣を… 持ち➡
He... wields eight blades...
左の頬に
牛の角の… 入れ墨が… ある。
And has bull horns tattooed on his...
left cheek.
《まったく
更に便利になっているね あの眼。
Sheesh...
Those eyes of his have improved.
ますます
面倒くさいヤツになっちゃったな》
Now he's even more difficult
to deal with.
《もう 更にかっこよく
なってんじゃんよ サスケ ヒヒヒッ》
Oh wow...
Sasuke's gotten even cooler.
《いいところだ。
衝動が抑えられそうだ。
This is a nice place...
I think I could control
my impulses here.
落ち着く》
It's calming...
"UNRAIKYO"
(キラービー)眼がいてえよ 光。
You make my eyes hurt...
Light...
もう昼か。 こんちくしょう。
Noon already?
Damn it, bastard! Screw you, man!
♪♪「バカ野郎 コノ野郎」
♪♪「朝から修業で お腹は空き過ぎ」
Training from mornin',
stomach so starvin'
♪♪「ラップ愛する オレ様好き者」
I'm just a rap-lovin' guy
♪♪「お昼の献立すき焼き決定 イエーイ」
and just decided on sukiyaki for lunch!
ん？
Yeah!
Hm...?!
アンタが八尾の人柱力か？
Are you the Jinchuriki host
of the Eight-Tails?
いや 八尾様ですか？ だろ。
No, it's Eight-Tails-sama. Okay?
そこ 人柱力様ですか？
だろ そこ。
Say, "Are you Jinchuriki-sama?" Okay?
アンタを拘束する。
I'm here to capture you.
♪♪「だから あなた様を
拘束させていただきます」
No. You have to say,
"Please allow me to capture you, sir."
だろ そこ！
Okay? Right?
水月は右。
Suigetsu, you take the right.
重吾は左。
Jugo, you take the left.
香燐は オレの後ろにつけ。
Karin, get behind me.
ん～ そうだな。
Hmm... Let's see.
♪♪「話の最中 途中」
Right in the middle of our conversation...
♪♪「大忠告だ バカ野郎 コノ野郎」
Here's some serious advice!
You're fools!
Fools.
人柱力は殺したらダメだって
暁のヤツらが言ってただろ 水月。
We can't kill the Jinchuriki.
Isn't that what the Akatsuki
told us, Suigetsu?
大丈夫だ。 ヤツのチャクラは
ちゃんと感じる。
It's all right.
I can feel his chakra.
ったく派手な陽動だぜ。
Geez, talk about a showy diversion.
クッ コイツ…。
Why you...!
オレ様に
突っ込んでいいのは オレだけだ。
The only one who gets
to dig me is me...
♪♪「すっこんでろ バカ野郎
パンチぶっこむぜ」
So scram, you fools, or I'll blast y'all!
♪♪「バカ野郎 イエーイ」
You fools... Yeah!
水月さがれ。
Suigetsu, get back.
♪♪「オレは覗きで お前は元気」
I'm peeking through...
And see you alive...
♪♪「見ているテメエら 能天気」
But y'all are so brainless!
ふざけるな！
Stop joking around!
♪♪「オレの殺気は オレの勇気
それはとっても前向き」
My thirst for blood is my courage...
Making me so optimistic.
♪♪「刀は回転 店は閉店」
My blades are swirlin',
but my store's a closin'.
♪♪「オレの技も 大安売り イエー」
Making for a blow-out sale
for my performance!
うおぉ～っ！
Yeah...
♪♪「余力を残して 魅力は光る」
I've got spare power and
my appeal is glowing,
♪♪「八尾がサビのキラービーだぜ オレ様が。
アー イエー」
Eight-Tails the bridge.
Killer Bee, that's me! Ah! Yay!
♪♪「戦い始めちまって 恥かくぜ。
ハジけるお前らに」
Start fighting and
you're gonna be embarrassed.
'Cuz you'll be torn apart...
あ… う…。
噛んだ…。
Bit my tongue...
な… なんだ コイツ。
Wh-What's with this guy?
こんな わけのわかんないヤツに
あの重吾が…。
He's totally crazy, but that Jugo...
《ボクの首切り包丁を
これほどまでに うまく…。
He keeps dodging
my Executioner's blade...
コイツ いったい…》
What is this guy?!
噛んだじゃねぇか バカ野郎。
You made me bite my tongue... Fools!
う… うぅ…。
(香燐)大丈夫か!?
あぁ…。
Are you all right?!
Yeah...
オレがいこう。
I'll go.
♪♪「お前ら 何者だ。
バカ野郎 この野郎」
Who the hell are you all?
Fools... You fools!
ふっざけやがって！ ホント コイツ！
This guy's getting on my nerves!
♪♪「お前ら 何様！
なにゆえ オレ様 捕まえる？ アー」
Who are you?
Why would you capture me? Huh?
お前に言う必要はない。
We don't owe you an explanation.
こんな 変に韻を踏んで
しゃべるようなヤツなんかと…。
A guy who talks in weird verses...
is such a pain to deal with.
とんだ おつかいだよ！
一刻も早く
力を手に入れるためだ。
It's to obtain power
as quickly as possible.
嫌なら 去れ。
If you don't like it, leave.
チッ！
Tsk...
《そりゃ キミの都合でしょ》
That's your prerogative...
あのときの口約束が ホントかウソか…
さっさと確認しておきたいしな。
I also want to confirm whether
the Akatsuki's verbal promise is
true or false and get it over with.
どちらにしろ
アイツら暁を利用するのは オレたちだ。
Either way, we're the ones who
are going to use the Akatsuki.
そのことは 頭に入れておけ。
Keep that in mind.
《暁？》
The Akatsuki?
当然だ。
That goes without question.
《か… かっけぇ サスケ！
Y-You are so cool, Sasuke!
やっぱり サスケは 駒になるような
ガラじゃねぇもんな！》
I knew he wouldn't let himself
be used as a pawn.
(水月)なら さっさと
その耳障りな ダジャレ野郎を➡
Well then, let's get to it and
silence this irritating rapper.
黙らせてしまおうよ。
そのつもりだ！
I intend to.
here are the answers of the path
koko ni aru no wa kimi ga ima made erande michi no
you chose up till now, look and go on by yourself
kotae tachi yo hora jishin motte susumeba ii
it's very natural, like a rainbow over
totemo shizen na no amaeagari no
asphalt after a rainfall
asufaruto ni niji ga kakaru you ni
a lonely wind blew and
lonely kaze ga fuite
a feeling dawned on me
feeling ki ga tsuita yo
there are any answers anywhere
kotae wo doko ni mo nai kedo
call me, I got it already
call me wakatteru wa
with you, we'll always
with you ai wa itsu mo
love each other
atae au mono
for you
I'm sure one day you will
kitto kimi wa itsu no hi ka
be able to fly in the sky
kono sora wo toberu hazu dakara
no matter how many times we've stumbled for you
nando tsumaizuta to shite mo for you
there's only one thing important
taisetsu na koto wa hitotsu
which is to dream
yumemiru koto
so at least keep your heart open
kokoro dake wa tozasanaide ite
Next Episode
Your illusions I obliterate,
then you all I shall annihilate!
My true form of the Jinchuriki...
ヒナタ。
え？ あ… はい。
It's a Monster, so watch it now,
Host Transformation, yeah.
この間 放送された
「ナ… ナルト君」って回➡
あれ なかなか
好評だったみたいだよ。
Eight-Tails will pee your pants,
you lil' ants!
特に 男子に。
えっ？
To spear my foes,
my glorious longhorns!
そ… そんな…。
Wheeeee!!!
でもさ 名前を言っただけで
人気が出るなんて➡
Such chakra...
Is this even possible?
すっげ～ってばよ ヒナタ！
なぁ？ サクラちゃん…。
Next time on Naruto Shippuden: "The Eight-Tails vs Sasuke"
The Eight-Tails vs Sasuke
なんで 私に話を振るわけ？
That's his... true form?!
なんなの！
この ヒロインとしての扱いの差は！
私だって 本気になれば
そのくらい…。
Hinata...
Huh? Y-Yes?!
That episode where you said,
"N-Naruto-kun"...
照れるとき！
ナルト君…。
I heard it was quite a hit.
嬉しいとき！
ナルト君！
Especially among the guys.
(ヒナタ)い… 色っぽく。
(サクラ)ナルト君。
Huh?! R-Really?
泣いて！
ナルト君！
(ヒナタ)慌てて！
ナルト君!?
You know, that's cool how
you can boost popularity
絶叫して！
ナルトく～ん！
just by saying names, Hinata!
はぁ… はぁ… どんなもんですか。
Right?! Sakura-chan...
Why look at me when you say that?
(音響監督)はい オッケーです。
と言いたいところだけど➡
Huh? Well...
Why this difference in
the treatment of heroines?
サクラは そんなセリフ言う予定ないんで
いりませ～ん。
はぁ!? ふざけんな！
しゃ～んなろ～っ！
If I get down to business, even I can...
- You're embarrassed.
- N-Naruto-kun...
(みんな)うわ～っ！
- When you're happy...
- Naruto-kun.
(ナツ)仕事だ 仕事だ！
- Erotic.
- Naruto-kun...
どれ どれ？
- Crying.
- N-Naruto.
(ハッピー)ナツ！ これは どう？
- Panicked.
- Naruto-kun.
- Screaming!
- N-Naruto-kun!
お尋ね者のベルベノを捕まえれば
400万ジュエルの報酬か。
How was that?
That's good...
Is what I'd like to say.
(ルーシィ)いいわね それ！
But Sakura won't be saying lines
like that.
今 お金が すっからかんだし
もう これに決定よ！
So we won't need them.
Huh?! Quit joking around. Shannaro!
"STUDIO"